In this video, we will learn how to reverse-activate and shrink the filter to complete a multi-layered clothing dress.
First, we will transfer the material to the work area.
In this case, I will add a little bit of T-shirt to show you later.
We create a belt plate and reverse-activate them.
After the plate is reversed, it will not participate in the simulation and there will be no conflict.
Select a set of plates and modify the tail shrink to make the clothes become tight.
Combine the belt plates together, then activate them and start the simulation.
Now the belt is correctly worn on the outside of the clothes.
Harden the belt to make it more stable and wrap it around the outside.
Then increase the tail shrink rate of the chain group to 100.
Now that the layer is stable, we will add another coat.
After the inner layer is worn, we can freeze all the inner layers.
Let them have a conflict with other layers while maintaining their shape.
Now we add a coat, start the simulation and adjust the shape of the clothes.